Welcome.
You find what you were looking for?
No. I could find it online, I bet. Easy.
Or you could ask a clerk to help.
Nah, there's no need. I'm independent.
Okay, I'm gonna go buy this.
You're checking out? I found something I want too. I'll come with you.
Tag!
Ow!
Know what they got over there? A huge treasure trove of gaming magazines!
Let's go!
Sure.
Sure!
What can you expect?
I'll explain the same part.
Didn't read the same time.
Even before we open, I gave my name goodbye.
Why are you doing so much?
Can you assume that you left me away?
Let's go.
you're giving me this to wear oh why the heck did I bring mine when I could
have just gone and grab yours it's fine so uh thank you I'll borrow yours
what's with the oversized jacket it's a long story where's Remy she left had to
head home early but she did stop by to open the window nice to see she's
staying on top of her window opening responsibility hey Sengoku what exactly
is it you like about her it's hard to believe you of all people are asking me
that why it seems like a normal question to me well normal subjective
guess I like how dependent she is she's not very strong so she needs me
around that's why you like having a weak girl by your side because it makes you
feel stronger in comparison hey don't get it twisted I don't control her or
anything I just have this urge to protect her I can't really explain it but I
have this powerful inclination to keep her safe and I like that feeling I'm not a
very strong person to begin with but for her sake I want to become the strongest
I've ever been despite all my limitations Remy's support helps me find that
strength though it's very give-and-take not a one-way street I push her as much as
she pushes me so she's the one protecting me in the end ironic kind of
like how she looks out for you right sakura
a little color in your cheeks makes you look cute
yeah I know what you mean now thank you Remy has a way of giving me courage too
it's the push I need the push to make me try a tiny bit harder
glad that's over with you got any plans after school Ishikawa
hey there how goes
thanks for lending me this sorry for the wait I wanted to run it through the wash
before I gave it back to you oh thanks but you didn't have to go out of your way
and do something like that I just wanted to show you the same courtesy you
showed me
dude come here real quick
coming
bye
hang on
I wound up making too many cookies please
what cookies so are you saying those are from me yes I hope you like them
oh these rock holy cow oh that sakura one was way good might just be my favorite
do you like sakura sakura yeah of course I do
Ishikawa calming breaths dude sorry to rush oh and I'm officially in love with these so please make more
it took you long enough give me a break
how lucky I snagged the last volume
yuki what gives you and I both know you've been looking for that
it's cool I think that girl wanted it more than I did
I'll eventually get one it's no biggie
Ishikawa got a visitor
coming
hey so I noticed that you and toru don't seem as close these days there a reason for that or
yeah well why would he spend time with me when he could be off eating cookies somewhere
what's that supposed to mean
I've only known yuki for three years but she's like an open book to me
oh yeah next period of study all for us sweetness
the more upset she is deep down the bigger her smile gets
even when she desperately wants something she won't admit it
and if the words I want this or I love this do manage to get out she never says them with all her heart
as a result the things yuki wants her loves tend to slip out of her reach
I appreciate you lending me your handkerchief and made these to say thanks
I'm okay
huh
no way cookies that's like a top three best snack
well thank you for the thank you
they really are bomb Kono
that's sweet of you to say
say it again cause they're freaking good
to say thanks
not bad
I might as well eat them if they ended up this tasty
how pathetic can I get
huh a cake
yeah
I could use the help since I've never made one before
it doesn't have to be super fancy or anything so long as it tastes yummy
but even that might be setting my standards too high
you know Yoshikawa
I wasn't born with the natural ability to bake
it came with practice
nobody is perfect at something right off the bat
if you mess up just give it another shot
great
wow
it took you seven days to bake these
so um they're cupcakes right
if you can't even tell that much then they're worse than I thought
I'm confused
why are you keeping your new hobby from toru
because he'd make fun of me and I don't need that aggravation
I don't think he would
especially if you knew that you were baking for him
these aren't for toru
what are you crazy
hey there you are
having a rooftop party and you didn't invite me
don't you dare look
is this a cupcake
give it back
wow
tastes disgusting
excuse you
like you're awful
I know
good grief
I can't wait for the next
same here
yeah me too
I'm all over it
so Miyamoto's absent today
because he's in Hokkaido
yeah he's visiting family up there for a memorial service
five whole days
which means he's gonna miss an entire week of school
wait a second
I'll have to read different lines out loud if he's not here
so which line was his
I think it was the fifth one wasn't it
dang it Miyamoto
mine's long now
and mine is way easier
then help me translate this Yoshikawa
made it to Hokkaido
it's a whole lot cooler
just the weather
though
my battery's almost dead
don't tell me I left my charger at home
hey uncle
do you have a spare charger
for my phone
sure
if they're compatible
all right
that's a no
can we go to the convenience store
I've got my hands tied cleaning up
I'm sorry honey
but I can't drive you anywhere right now
whatever you need
I'm sure you can get it later
are you gonna drink too?
yeah
I'm super thirsty today
that's one way to stay hydrated in this heat
that sugary stuff doesn't hydrate you
just makes you fat
just three more days
see you tomorrow honey
yeah see ya
are you waiting for someone?
why would I be?
bye
Kyoko
that's not my bowl sweetheart
of course not
it's my bros
what you trying to trigger me or something?
surprisingly no
I made a mistake is all
Sota
check and see if there are flying pigs outside
oh
today's the day Miyamoto comes back
will he get in by dinner time?
or
nah
I have no idea
you're killing me sissy
hurricane star already started and you're making me miss it
didn't realize you were such a news buff
our next story tonight
delays at airports caused by further carry-on restrictions
hormones
am I right?
wait
Kyoko?
and it's back
shindo
Ishikawa says
the big test got postponed
that sucks
I actually studied
Izumi?
you see?
yo
excuse me
You're here.
Dummy.
Up until that point, I never knew how long five days could feel.
I'm glad that you're home.
Uh, yeah, thanks. Good to see you.
Now I know that time apart can be torture.
Something Miyamoto doesn't like?
That would have to be...
Horror movies.
Though he's not opposed to marathoning them with me.
So maybe he's cool with them after all.
Or he's enduring them for you.
A few words of advice?
Ditch the scary stuff before he ditches you.
It's only a matter of time.
Huh?
Plus, cute girls finding glee from watching slasher flicks is a special kind of creepy.
I'm not that cute.
Come on, ladies.
Ori, you're missing the entire point.
Remy has to agree with Yoshikawa on this one.
That sounds like a total turn-off.
Huh.
I guess.
I brought a movie for us to watch tonight.
It's got doggos.
So, what do you say?
Or let's watch, right behind you, The Third Nightmare.
Yeah, let's.
You need to ditch the scary stuff before he ditches you.
It's only a matter of time.
So, um, I'm kind of nervous.
This movie might get pretty hairy.
Hope I can hack it.
I think you'll hack it just fine.
Compared to the gore fest we've watched on our past movie nights, this should be a cakewalk.
You're a professional.
Strike one.
Pretend to be afraid so he can comfort you.
So scary!
You scared the pants off me.
There goes strike two.
Maybe this tactic's a lost cause.
You could always give hand-holding during the movie a try.
I-I sure am petrified.
All I want to do is enjoy a movie with him.
I'm sorry I'm such a wimp.
I really am.
It's nothing you have to apologize for!
Getting a little jumpy isn't a big deal!
I know.
Just give me a second.
I need a moment.
No.
He's gonna dump me, isn't he?
Strike three!
I'm pitiful.
What is she doing?
You okay?
I'm not okay, and I'm not cute.
Hey now, you're cute.
You're very cute.
I don't get scared.
I can't even act scared.
I'm just a hopeless, uncute excuse for a human.
So all that stuff you pulled in the living room was you trying to act more cute for me?
Not like it matters, dummy.
If it was, I'm sorry.
I-I was too busy freaking out to even see.
Sorry I didn't notice you.
Why is it that you keep apologizing to me?
Don't look, you big dummy!
I think you're the big dummy this time.
I didn't fall for just some cute girl, you know.
I fell in love with you.
Let's finish the movie.
That sound like a plan?
Oh, wow.
That's really coming down.
Yeah, sure is.
I'm the same.
I fell for him just as hard.
I fell for his long eyelashes
and the way he scares so easily.
I fell for his sarcastic quips
and how his slender frame feels in my arms.
His voice.
I-I fell for...
Izumi.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm listening to your heart.
And you can understand what it's telling you?
It's saying how cold it is.
You're freezing.
Your hands and ears are like ice.
Probably from the rain.
Probably.
There's no way you're going home,
not in this downpour.
There was a fire within me.
And I wanted Miyamura to feel it too.
It's you, me, and Sissy having fun!
What's wrong?
You know, she's my big sister.
Wait a minute.
Sota, are you worried that I'm taking her away?
I won't.
She'll always be your big sis.
And what about you?
What else?
I'll always be your big bro.
I promise I won't take your sister from you.
But could I maybe have Kyoko?
Okay.
Yeah.
You're not me.
Okay.
Later, I was seen through my dreams
And the bright night is to consider
It's back to you
Mr. slight rolling
This gives you being a bright bright night
You'll also write you back
This is my ghost
姿が名残惜しくって
長袖のシャツに見覚えある道
少し寂しそうに見えた
胸が苦しくなるけど暖かい
気付いた冬の朝だ
約束するよ
近くにいるから見えないものほど
大事にするよ
言葉にできないんだけどね
アメリカの髪を見つけたら